《盲点》前情回顾
Previously on "Blindspot"...
卡特助理局长失踪了  推测已死亡
Assistant Director Carter is missing, presumed dead.
什么
What?
我们或许应该谈谈昨晚的事
We should probably talk about last night.
我住的那条街  街尾有个公园
There's a park at the end of my street.
我们十点在那儿见
Meet me there at 10:00.
我们讨论了和威勒探员划清界限的问题
We discussed setting clearer boundaries with Agent Weller.
进展如何
How's that been going?
还不错
Good.
他们怕你  也确实该怕
They're scared of you... and they should be.
我有任务要交给你
I have missions for you.
得按我的方式来
We do this on my terms.
这些就是你的方式
These are your terms.
这都是你的计划
This is all your plan.
实施的时候到了
And it's time to get started.
现在要干什么
So what now?
现在
Now...
这是你第一个任务
your first mission.
这是什么
What is that?
这是梅菲尔那支钢笔的复制品
It's an exact replica of Mayfair's pen.
你怎么知道梅菲尔的笔是什么样子
How do you know what Mayfair's pen looks like?
你们安装了摄像头了吗
Do you have cameras in there?
没有  我们...自有办法
No, we... we have another way.
我需要你把她的笔掉包
I need you to swap 'em
带来交给我
and bring me hers.
你们抹去了我的记忆
So you wipe my memory,
给我全身纹了纹身
you tattoo my entire body,
然后把我送进联调局
and then you send me to the FBI
就为了让我偷一支笔
so I can steal a pen.
怎么了
What?
你...你还是一点没变啊
You're still-- you're still you.
这到底是什么
What is it?
监听器  追踪器
A bug? A tracker?
我绝对不会背叛我的队友
Because I won't betray my team.
这不是背叛  就是一支笔而已
It's not a betrayal, it's a pen.
普通的笔
A regular pen.
我怎么知道不是你
How do I know that you weren't
拿枪逼着我说出视频里那番话
holding a gun to my head during that video?
我从没拿枪指着你过
I've never pointed a gun at you.
我没那么傻
I know better.
如果你真这么以为  你就不会来了
And if you really thought that, you wouldn't be here.
你会把你的队友带来
You'd have sent your team.
但是你没有
But you didn't...
因为冥冥之中
because, somehow...
你知道自己不属于他们中的一员
you know that you're not one of them,
你只是他们团队里的一颗齿轮而已
that you're just a cog in their machine.
有用的时候就百般拉拢
Welcome while useful,
失去价值了就立马抛弃
disposable the second you're not.
闯进我安全屋的那个男人是怎么回事
What about the man at my safe house...
有胡子的那个
with the beard?
他是你们的人吗
Was he with you?
和我们一起的吗
With us?
把那支笔拿来给我
Bring me that pen
我就告诉你更多答案
and I'll give you more answers.
等他起来吃的时候都被果酱泡软了
It's gonna get soggy by the time he eats it.
你得先把两片都涂上花生酱
You got to put peanut butter on both sides first
果酱夹在中间
and jelly in the middle.
抱歉  没看出来你还是果酱三明治大师
Oh, sorry, I had no idea you were such an expert on PB&J.
我还真是
Well, that I am.
要我给你示范一下吗
So... do you want me to show you?
-您请  -好的
- By all means. - Okay.
给我吧  好好学着
Give me that, watch and learn.
我今天得晚点回来了
So, um, I'm gonna be home late tonight.
他叫什么
What's his name?
倒不如你先告诉我  你昨晚去见谁了
How about you tell me who you were meeting with last night?
我估计你也不会说
Okay, I didn't think so.
我只是提前跟你打个招呼
I'm just, uh, giving you the heads-up
因为我让爸来看孩子了
'cause Dad's gonna babysit,
免得你不想看见他
in case you wanted to be somewhere else.
我们没事
We'll be fine.
再来点
A bit more.
你们在匡蒂科就是学这些的吗
Is that what they teach you in Quantico?
再给我做一份吧
Now you can make me one, too.
我上班要迟到了
I'm late for work.
自己做吧
Make it yourself.
烦死人了你
You are so mean.
哥们
Yo, buddy.
你还好吗
You okay?
迷路了你
You lost?
你在那个军事基地上班吗
You-- you work down the base there?
我载你一程吧
Let me give you a ride.
上午好
Morning.
我想为昨晚的事道歉
I want to say sorry about last night.
我应该告诉你我来不了的
I should've told you that I wasn't coming.
我们两个...
The two of us...
太纠缠不清了
it's too complicated.
是啊
Right.
我也想这么说来着
I was gonna say the same thing.
好  我很高兴我们想到一起去了
Okay, I'm glad we're on the same page.
我...我不想把关系弄得太尴尬
I don't-- I don't want things to be awkward.
是  当然不会
No, of course not.
贝克堡军事基地
你有什么事吗
Can I help you?
是的  我在前面半英里处发现了这孩子
Yeah, I picked up this kid about a half mile back.
他有空降兵纹身
He's got an airborne tat,
但我觉得他脑袋好像出了点问题
but, uh, I don't think he's right in the head.
你们能过去看看吗
You think you guys could check him out?
请下车
Can you step out of the car, please?
你叫什么名字  士兵
What's your name, soldier?
-过来  -不
- Come on. - No.
不  你不能带走我
No, you can't take me.
没关系  我们是来帮你的
It's okay, we're here to help you.
你不能这么对我们  住手
You can't do this to us, stop!
别乱动  小子
Stay where you are, son!
三名受害者被宣告死亡
Three of the victims were declared dead,
一人正在医院抢救
one is in the hospital,
枪手仍然逍遥法外
and the shooter is still on the loose.
身份确认了吗
Do we have an ID?
陆军中士查理·纳比尔
Army Sergeant Charlie Napier.
三次驻军伊拉克  胸前挂满了勋章
Three tours in Iraq, jacket full of medals.
查理·纳比尔
这种情况通常在宪宾队的管辖范围之内
This is usually Military Police jurisdiction.
我知道  这些字母碎片
I know... these are letter fragments
位于简的左腿后侧
that are on the back of Jane's left leg
它们被四等分并加以旋转
that are divided into quarters and then rotated.
就像散落在桌子上的一箱子拼图碎片
It's like a box of puzzle pieces scattered on a table.
当你把它们拼凑起来...
When you fit them together...
中士
查理·纳比尔
我们早就破解了这条信息
We decoded this one already.
但是当我的团队调查过之后
But when my team looked into it,
发现这是条死胡同
it was a dead end.
向他问过话吗
Did we question him?
-没法问  -为什么
- We couldn't. - Why not?
因为查理·纳比尔早在十八个月前就死了
Because Charlie Napier died 18 months ago.
在伊拉克的一次行动中  死于土制炸弹爆炸
Killed in action, an IED explosion in Iraq.
一个死人怎么能在军事基地开枪
How's a dead man shoot up a military base?
更重要的是  他的下一个目标是谁
And, more importantly, what's he gonna shoot up next?
盲   点
第一季  第十二集
我们还知道关于这家伙的其它信息吗
What else do we know about this guy?
军队模范
Army poster child,
高中时就应征入伍
enlisted straight out of high school,
把每一分钱都寄回家
sent every penny home
帮他的单亲母亲维持生计
to a single mother to help pay the bills.
能确定这是同一个人吗
Are we sure it's the same guy?
我已经将这个视频跟我们手上的所有
I've run this video through every biometric
生物识别扫描信息一一比对过了
recognition scan we've got.
面部  声音  耳朵  是他没错
Face, voice, ear-- it's him.
耳朵  真的吗
Ear, really?
耳朵包含很多重要信息
Oh, the ear's a treasure trove.
我能从耳朵挖掘出的信息说出来能吓到你
You don't even want to know what I can do with an ear.
是弄错了  还是有人想掩盖什么
Was this a screw-up or a cover-up?
那个炸弹爆炸的威力非常可怕
The IED explosion was pretty gruesome,
所以他们没办法找全四分五裂的尸体
so they weren't able to recover a body.
但他们通过查理的牙齿和组织确认了身份
But they ID'd Charlie off of dental and tissue samples.
看来某间实验室完全判断错误了
So some lab made a terrible mistake.
或者就是有人想让他消失
Or someone really wanted him off the grid.
那些是什么
Hey, what are those?
更多的名字
More names.
其他四位士兵  全部遭受过不同的袭击
Four other soldiers, all different attacks,
全部阵亡  就像查理一样
all KIA, just like Charlie.
既然查理还活着
So if Charlie's alive,
那么这些士兵也有可能还活着
then these other soldiers could be, too.
查理说过"你不能这么对我们"
Charlie said, "You can't do this to us."
他可能还有其他同伴
He could be a part of a cell.
也就是说接下来恐怕会出现更多袭击事件
Which means there could be more attacks coming.
他为什么要跟他曾经守卫的人民反目
Why would he turn against his own people like that?
个人仇恨  不满体制  创伤应激障碍
Personal vendetta, institutional grudge, PTSD?
他的档案里没有列出任何
His file didn't list any history
反人类或者精神病病史
of insubordination or mental illness.
是  他的档案还注明他已死亡呢
Yeah, but his file also listed him as dead.
稍等
Hang on.
查理刚才用那辆卡车司机的手机
Charlie just used the truck driver's cell phone
拨打了一个已停机的号码
to call an out-of-service landline.
是他儿时的故居
It's his childhood home.
他母亲现在还住在那里吗
Does his mother still live there?
没有  她最近搬到北部去了
No, she moved upstate recently.
对  但要是他真的消失了很久
Yeah, but if he was off the grid,
他是不会知道的
he wouldn't know that.
你觉得他是在找藏身之处吗
You think he was looking for someplace to lay low?
想知道只有一个办法
One way to find out.
出发吧
Let's move.
拜托了  拜托  帮帮我  他有枪
Please, please, help! He has a gun!
女士  请到车后躲避一下
All right, ma'am, get behind that car.
待在那儿
You stay there.
里德  萨帕塔  从房子后面包抄
Reade, Zapata, go around the back.
我和简从前门进去
Me and Jane will go through the front.
我们是联调局的  放下武器
This is the FBI. Drop the weapon.
跪在地上
Get down on your knees.
我妈妈在哪
Where's my mom?
你们对她干了什么
What did you do with her?
放下武器  跪在地上
Drop the weapon and get down on your knees.
快
Now.
我真的撑不下去了
I can't take it anymore.
我撑不下去了
I can't take it.
如果你们撑不下去了  就去那边敲钟
If you can't take it, then ring that bell!
前进  前进  前进
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
你速度得快点
You're gonna have to move faster!
这不是你待的地方  小公主
You don't belong here, princess!
来吧  摇铃吧
Let's go, ring it!
干脆摇铃退出得了
Ring that damn bell and quit!
查理  放下武器  跪在地上
Charlie, put down the weapon and get down on your knees.
求你了  我不能回去
Please... I can't go back there.
我不想回去
I won't go back.
回哪去
Go back where?
我只想见我妈
I just want my mom.
她在这  查理
She's here, Charlie.
你妈妈就在楼下
Your mom's downstairs.
她想和你聊聊  好吗
She wants to talk to you, okay?
所以把枪放下
So just put the gun down
然后我们去告诉她你一切都好
and let's go tell her that you're okay.
好吗
All right?
她在等你  查理
She's waiting for you, Charlie.
我们下楼
Let's go down there.
没事的
It's okay.
-妈  不  放开我  -过来
- Mama! No, no! - Come here, come here.
不要
No!
我说过了  我不记得
I told you, I don't remember.
你不记得你过去一年半
You don't remember where you've been
去了哪里吗
for the last year and a half?
对
No.
你记得的最后一件事是什么
What's the last thing you do remember?
一个地牢
A dungeon.
火焰
Flames.
这个地牢在哪
And where was this dungeon?
查理  你当时在哪
Charlie, where were you?
我在地狱
I was in hell...
被恶魔折磨
being tortured by the devil.
恶魔长什么样
What did this devil look like?
我不要和你说话
I'm not talking to you.
你骗了我
You lied to me.
你必须得想起来  查理
You have to try to remember, Charlie.
当时你身边有谁
Who was there with you?
地狱是什么样子
What did hell look like?
你是怎么出来的
How'd you get out?
我游过了一条河
I swam across a river.
什么河
What river?
冥河
The River Styx.
化验显示查理体内有氨基丙苯
Charlie's tested positive for amphetamines,
兴奋剂  类固醇和麻醉剂
stimulates, steroids, and anesthetics.
即使很小的剂量
Even in low doses,
这些药物结合起来会致人衰弱
the combination of these drugs is massively debilitating.
而查理体内的含量惊人
And Charlie's levels are off the charts.
这就解释了他的行为
Well, that would explain his behavior.
但引起我注意的不是药的剂量
But it's not the volume that caught my eye.
其中一剂药物就是泽塔互作蛋白
One of the drugs used was Zeta Interacting Protein.
泽塔互作蛋白
等一下  这好像
Wait, like--
对  就是用来清除你记忆的药物
Yes, exactly the same drug that was used to erase your memory.
泽塔互作蛋白
查理体内含有过量复杂合成物
Charlie's body was overloaded with very complix composite.
其中就有泽塔互作蛋白
And ZIP was part of it?
对
Yes.
所以这其中定有联系
So there's got to be a connection.
泽塔互作蛋白不罕见  但你的事之前
Well, ZIP isn't a rare drug, but until your case,
我还没见过剂量这么高的
I'd never seen it used in such high doses.
所以他们的剂量一样吗
So are the levels similar here?
并不一样高  但差不多
Well, not quite as high, but close.
所以对查理做出这些的
So the people that did this to Charlie
可能和简的是同一批人
could be the same people that did this to Jane.
你对自己做了这些
You did this to yourself.
是你对自己做了这些
You... did this... to yourself.
可能是  但也有可能
Maybe, but there's also a possibility
这和她一点关联也没有
this might have nothing to do with her.
或者和她大有关联
Or it could have everything to do with her.
所以我们得找到这些人
So we got to find these people.
别的药物呢
What about these other drugs?
医生可以出于合理医用目的开这些药吗
Do they have any legitimate medical purpose?
单独开的话  可以
Individually, yes.
但这种组合和剂量
But with this combination and quantity,
查理·纳比尔  药物化验分析
基本上会导致病人昏迷不醒
most patients would be comatose.
为什么查理没有
So why not Charlie?
这也是我的疑惑之处
Well, that's what's been baffling me.
他的肾上腺素是正常水平的十倍
His epinephrine levels are 10 times the normal limit.
交感神经系统极度兴奋
His entire sympathetic system is surging.
他的心率和血压都失衡了
His heart rate, blood pressure, they're out of control.
类固醇用来提升体能
Steroids to improve physical performance,
麻黄素用来提高精神敏锐度
ephedrine to sharpen mental acuity,
及改变情绪的药物来抑制恐惧
and mood-altering drugs to dampen fear.
这个人一直处于应激状态
This guy is in a constant state of fight-or-flight.
有人想创造出更"优秀"的士兵
Someone's trying to build a better soldier.
我们军方曾做过这样的事
Our military has a history with this,
把不知情的士兵当小白鼠
using unwitting soldiers to test everything
从致幻剂到生化武器都试了个遍
from LSD to chemical weapons.
如果查理当时在他们那
If they got Charlie,
其他四个士兵可能也在
they could have the four other soldiers.
对  但我们怎么找到他们
Yeah, but how do we find them?
就算真是军事行动
If it is a military operation,
五角大楼也不会轻易告诉我们在哪的
the Pentagon isn't just gonna tell us where they are.
而且我们的证人也算不上个可靠情报源
And our witness isn't exactly a font of information.
查理体内泽塔互作蛋白的含量没有简的高
Charlie's ZIP levels aren't as high as Jane's.
他能在几周之内逐渐恢复记忆
He can start recovering memories within a few weeks.
我们等不了那么久
We can't afford to wait that long.
我看到熟悉的场景会触发记忆
Familiar sights trigger memories for me.
查理想见他妈妈
Charlie wants his mom.
如果我们能把她带来
If we could get her here,
也许他会想起更多事情
maybe more memories would come back.
他可能会记起来他被关在了哪里
He might remember where he was being held
找到查理的母亲
Let's track down Charlie's mother.
查理
Charlie?
我的天
Oh, my God.
真的是你
It is you.
他们跟我说你死了
They told me you were dead.
宝贝
Baby...
我  我以为我失去你了
I-- I thought I lost you.
妈妈  对不起
Mom, I-I'm sorry.
我每夜都为你祈祷
I prayed for you every night.
查理  你去哪了
Oh, Charlie... Where did you go?
我去了地狱  但我逃出来了
I was in hell, but I got out.
我看见了上帝
I saw the face of God.
妈妈  他叫我回家  回到你身边
Mom, he told me to go home to you.
天啊
Oh, God.
她儿子杀了三个人
Her son killed three people
而她想做的只是拥抱他
and all she wants to do is hug him.
他回到她身边了
She got him back.
这对她来说足够了
It's all she cares about.
为什么你还不肯原谅你父亲
Why haven't you forgiven your father?
你知道他没有...
You know he didn't...
那天晚上的事是你误会了
that you were wrong about that night.
事情比你想的要复杂
It's more complicated than that.
你总是这么说  那...
You always say that, but...
为什么  有什么复杂的
Why? What's so complicated?
他曾是个糟糕的父亲
He was a terrible father.
不闻不问  日夜酗酒
He was distant. He was drunk.
我误会了一晚的事也不能改变这一切
Me being wrong about one night doesn't change any of that.
但他病了  不是吗
But he's sick, right?
纹身上列出的其他士兵的情况有进展了吗
Any progress on the other soldiers listed on the tattoo?
还没
Uh, nothing yet.
我交叉对比了他们在哪训练
I cross-referenced where they trained,
在哪服役  和在哪长大的信息
where they served, where they grew up.
继续挖掘
Keep digging.
在查理身上做实验的人
Whoever was experimenting on Charlie
可能对其他四人也做了相同的实验
is probably doing the same to the other four.
我们必须找到他们
We have to track them down.
你说找到谋害大卫的凶手后
You said you were gonna take a leave of absence
你就打算申请探员休假的
after we found David's killer.
我知道  我是打算的
I know, I was.
但后来发生了泛亚921的那事
But then there was the whole Pan-Asian 921 thing
接着又这件
and then this...
就感觉这里的事更为重要
Things here just feel more important.
我是过来人
I've been where you are,
我当时的处理方式也跟你一模一样
and I dealt with it in the exact same way.
起过一阵子的作用
And it worked for a while.
你逃避得越久
The longer you run from this,
到逃不掉的那天它就伤你越深
the more it will hurt when it catches you.
相信我  你逃不掉的
And, trust me, it will catch you.
我得继续工作了
I should get back to work.
放开我
Let me go!
求你别让他们带走我
Please, don't let them take me!
怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
他们是刑事调查局的人  说归他们管
They're CID claiming that they have jurisdiction.
特别探员肯恩·索普
Special Agent Ken Thorpe,
陆军刑事调查司令部
Army Criminal Investigation Command,
这本来就归我们管
and we do have jurisdiction.
我们调查还没结束
We're in the middle of an investigation.
他触犯了联邦罪行
He committed a federal crime.
在陆军管辖范围
On Army land.
受害者是陆军  他也是陆军
The victims were Army, he's Army.
你和你的人别插手
You and your team need to stand down.
我们有理由认为那个男人遭受了
We have reasons to believe that that man has been subjected
非人道的医学试验
to inhumane medical experiments.
在此之前陆军宣告他死了
After the Army had declared him dead.
所以你能理解为什么我们不太愿意
So you can understand why we're reluctant
把他交给你们了吧
to hand him back to you.
我对那一无所知
I don't know anything about that.
你们知道就会告诉我们了吗
And you'd say if you did, right?
打给你上司
Call your boss.
打给我上司  就算打给总统
Call my boss. Hell, call the president.
他们都会跟你说同样的话
They'll all tell you the same thing.
这是我的案子
This is my case.
让他们走
Let them go.
你就任由他这么做吗
You're just gonna let this happen?
-退下  -求你别让他们把我带回那里
- Stand down. - Don't let them take me back there... please.
有件事能把简纹身上的所有士兵联系起来
I found something linking all the soldiers on Jane's tattoo.
他们互相认识吗
Did they know each other?
他们活着的时候不认识
Not while they were alive.
五人都是被声称在土制炸弹爆炸中身亡
All five were declared dead in IED attacks.
而且每起爆炸案
And in every case,
第一支到达现场的急救队
the first responders on the scene
都来自同一家私人军事承包商
were the same private military contractor.
哪家
Who?
诺斯莱克
Northlake.
为什么这么久才发现这层关系
Why'd it take this long to make that connection?
这种承包商一般都不喜欢曝光
Contractors like this go out of their way to be opaque.
每支急救队都是由不同机构资助的
Each of the responders were paid by separate entities.
但全都受诺斯莱克控制  对吗
But Northlake controls all of them?
他们掩盖得非常好  但的确是这样
They make it very hard to uncover, but yes.
军方医疗人员得好几个小时
It could've taken hours for the military M.Es
才能赶到袭击现场
to arrive at the attack site.
诺斯莱克有充分的时间处理那些尸体
Northlake would've had access to those bodies the entire time.
所以诺斯莱克绑架了这些军人
So Northlake kidnapped these soldiers,
制造他们死亡的假象
faked their deaths.
真正在进行这些实验的其实是他们
They're the ones responsible for running these experiments.
这可以说得通
Well, it makes sense.
私人军事承包商存在动机
Private military contractors have the motive
他们在为雇佣兵开发这些药品
to develop these drugs for the mercenaries.
另一群没有道德良知的人
Not the most morally scrupulous, either.
我们出发
Let's move.
别碰我
Leave me alone!
你们是谁  你们想干什么
Who are you? What do you want from me?
所有刑事调查局的探员都当场死亡
All the CID agents were dead on the scene.
查理呢
What about Charlie?
他失踪了
He's missing.
这是一次精准的军事化协同攻击
This attack was coordinated, military-style precision,
绝对是诺斯莱克的行事风格
definitely Northlake's M.O.
你觉得他们会杀了他吗
Do you think they'll kill him?
不会
No.
他们有理由让他活着
They wanted him alive for a reason.
我们最大的希望就是找到
Our best bet is to track down
他们进行这些实验的地方
where they've been conducting these experiments.
有没有查到他被关在哪里
Do we know anything yet about where he was being held,
除了"地狱"之外
outside of "Hell"?
有个司机让查理搭车
That driver that picked up Charlie,
当时是在哪
where was that?
早上八点  在贝克堡基地前的路上
Down the road from Fort Beck at about 8:00 a.m.
立即定位
Drop a pin in it.
博登的毒理报告不是缩小了
Didn't Borden's toxicology report
贝克堡
军事基地
查理最后一次被下药的时间范围吗
narrow down the last time Charlie was drugged?
对  在早上七点半左右
Yeah, at around 7:30 a.m.
好的  所以他大概跑了半小时
All right, so he's been on the run for half an hour,
最多跑了六到八公里
could've covered four to five miles at most.
贝克堡
军事基地
查理不是说他逃出来之后
Didn't Charlie say he swam across the River Styx
游过了冥河吗
after he escaped?
他被药物搞得神志不清了
He was drugged out of his mind.
对  但是如果他其实游过了其他东西呢
Yeah, but what if he swam across something?
比如说一条真的河
A real river.
贝克堡
军事基地
那有帮助
Well, that helps.
范围还是很大
It's still a lot of ground to cover.
听听这个
Hey, here's something.
初步报告显示
So the preliminary reports say,
袭击查理押运车的其中一个枪手
one of the gunman who attacked Charlie's transport
留下了一个带有油性残留的脚印
left a boot print with oil residue.
六号燃油
Heating oil number six,
纽约从2010年就开始淘汰这种油了
which New York started phasing out in 2010.
他们关押他的地方
Wherever they held him,
肯定有一个那种燃油的锅炉
they must've had one of those boilers there.
印证了他看到的火焰
The flames he saw.
有多少建筑还在用那种燃油
How many buildings still use that heating oil?
根据环保署的记录
According to EPA records,
在这范围内  只有五栋
in our radius, it's just five.
足够我们查下去了
It's enough to go on.
查理  我还以为见不到你了
Charlie, I thought we lost you.
别担心  我们很快就会离开这里
Don't worry, we're leaving here soon.
一切很快就会结束了
It'll all be over before you know it.
我们那五栋楼里的第一栋
First of our five buildings
应该在三公里之后出现
should be coming up in half a mile.
我们怎么知道要哪栋
How will we know what to look for?
没办法  我们得一栋一栋的找
We won't... we have to clear them one by one.
附近地标
等等  查理说他出来的时候
Wait, Charlie said he saw the face of God
看到了上帝之脸
when he came out.
按一下语音控制按钮
Hit the voice command button.
请说出命令
Please say a command.
目的地  迪非逊大道912号
Destination, 912 Division Ave.
上帝之脸在迪非逊大道912号
The face of God is at 912 Division?
可以这么说吧
Kinda.
上帝之脸
Face of God.
干得漂亮  塔莎
Nice work, Tasha.
那是我们要找的五栋楼之一
That's one of our five buildings.
查理出来的时候可以看到教堂
Charlie would've had a view of the church on his way out.
出发
Let's move.
你想要拉响那个铃
You want to ring that bell,
不是吗  公主
don't you, princess?
我们都知道你想放弃
We all know you want to quit.
不
No.
我们都知道你会放弃
We all know you gonna quit.
所以别再浪费我们的时间
So quit wasting our time
快去把那该死的铃拉响
and ring that damn bell!
简
Jane?
这个死了
This one's dead.
这个也是
Same here.
四名士兵  五张床
Four soldiers. Five beds.
查理还在他们手上
They still have Charlie.
诺斯莱克一定意识到情况危险了
Northlake must've figured the heat was on.
他们匆匆离开了这里
They left this place in a hurry.
还销毁了所有证据
And destroyed all the evidence behind them.
没有全部销毁
They didn't destroy everything.
我从其中一个损坏的硬盘里
I recovered a partial video file
恢复了一段视频文件
off one of the damaged hard drives.
他们认为删除文件就能防止...
They thought deleting them would stop them from--
如果你想销毁硬盘
If you want to destroy a hard drive,
用高能磁铁或者...
use a high-powered magnet or--
好吧  你发现了什么
All right, what'd you find?
42号试验  实验对象三
Trial 42, subject three,
主测试人斯派西诺博士
Dr. Sparacino principal examiner.
我在尝试最新的变体
I'm attempting my latest variant.
调整劳拉西泮[镇定剂]含量以减轻癫痫
Adjusting lorazepam levels to reduce seizures.
只有4号实验对象的大脑
Subject four's brain is the only one
能够成功负荷过量的肾上腺素
effectively processing the epinephrine overload.
看起来副作用只有轻度幻觉
Mild hallucinations seem to be the only side effect.
探索其中原因
Further experimentation is needed
有待进一步实验
in order to explore this.
视频结束
查理是唯一成功的研究对象
Charlie was the only one that it was working on.
因此他们抢回查理  把剩下的都杀了
That's why they stole him back and killed the others.
这个博士有什么背景
What do we know about that doctor?
琳赛·斯派西诺博士
Doctor Lindsay Sparacino.
在军队先进医学研究部
Served two decades in the Army's
工作了二十年
advanced medical research department.
2005年退休
Retired in '05.
很好  她一直没闲着
Nice, she's been keeping busy.
还有这个  这位博士把全部资产
But get this, the good doctor emptied all her assets
转移到海外账户了
into an offshore account.
她准备逃跑了
She's getting ready to run.
她可以把配方卖给恐怖组织
She could sell that formula to any terrorist cell
或大手笔的流氓国家
or rogue nation with an open checkbook.
于是他们就有了改造的超能军队
And they'd have an army full of engineered super soldiers.
前提是它有效
Only if it works.
那段视频似乎表明  查理的生理情况
That video makes it look like Charlie's biology is the key
是配方的关键
to unlocking the formula.
但我们得在她潜逃之前救回查理
But we need to get him back before she goes underground.
派人盯住方圆数百里范围内的
Let's put out a BOLO at every airport and port
所有机场码头
within 100 miles.
等等
Hang on.
我想她还没准备走
I don't think she's leaving just yet.
她的"简易通"刚显示穿过布鲁克林炮台隧道
Her EZ-Pass just dinged outside Brooklyn Battery Tunnel,
布鲁克林炮台隧道
从皇后区高速公路向东去了
going east on the BQE.
她曾在两英里外租了间仓库
She does rent a storage unit about two miles away.
她可能有堆积如山的现金和护照
She's probably got a stash of passports and cash.
或另一间实验室
Or another lab.
简是对的
Jane's right.
查理能负荷的剂量和别人不同
Charlie processed this cocktail differently,
那个博士需要弄清原因
and the doctor needs to find out why.
而且答案就深埋在
And the answers are probably buried deep
他的脑神经突触中
in the synapses of his brain.
她要对查理做什么
What is she gonna do to him?
反正不会让他活下来
Nothing that Charlie would live through.
沃尔默仓库
不用让他彻底失去知觉吗
Aren't we gonna put him all the way under?
不用  我要监测他的大脑活动
No... I need to monitor his brain activity
和知觉反应
and conscious responses.
你没有足够...
We don't have enough--
不出十分钟他就会死
he'll be dead within 10 minutes.
十分钟足够了
That's enough time.
如果研制好血清
We get this serum right,
我们就能让现代战争改头换面
we change the face of modern warfare.
帕特森说去六楼6-117单元
Patterson says the unit is 6-117, sixth floor.
没事  查理  不会疼太久的
It's okay, Charlie, it won't hurt for long.
里德  萨帕塔  去右路
Reade, Zapata, go right.
简  跟着我
Jane, with me.
清洁工具室
简  我的六点方向
Jane, on my six!
6-177单元
联调局  把东西放下  放下
FBI! Put that down. Put it down!
走过来
Walk towards me.
去那边
Get over there.
把手放墙上
Hands on the wall.
没事了  我们救你出去
It's okay, we're gonna get you safe.
你们是谁  对我有什么企图
Who are you? What do you want with me?
不  ZIP
Oh, no. ZIP.
他们又对他用药了
They dosed him again.
他不记得我们了
He can't remember us.
不  查理  别走
No-- Charlie, no!
简
Jane!
过来  靠墙站着
Come here, stay against that wall.
别动
Don't move.
看着他们
They're yours.
简
Jane!
-过来  -转过来
- Move. - Turn around.
查理  站住
Charlie, stop!
查理  等等
Charlie, wait.
离我远点儿
Get away from me!
拜托
Please.
我把它放地上
I'm gonna put this down.
我并不想伤害你
Please, I don't want to hurt you.
没事的
It's okay.
查理  别这样
Charlie, please don't.
求你  住手吧
Please, stop.
查理  我不想伤害你
Charlie, I don't want to hurt you.
查理  快停下来
Charlie, stop!
别这样
No, please.
不
No.
-你当时没必要...-但我还是开枪了
- You didn't have to... - Yeah, I did.
否则躺在尸体袋里的人可能就是你
It could've been you in that body bag.
他是无辜的
He was innocent.
他也不愿变成这样
He never wanted any of this.
只要有人威胁到我的团队或是你
Someone puts my team at risk or you at risk,
我绝不手软
I don't second guess.
事情有时候比看起来要复杂得多
Things can be more complicated than they seem.
在这一行里  只有好人跟坏人之分
In this job there are good guys and there are bad guys.
其实没那么复杂
It's not that complicated.
你刚刚受伤了
You took some hits.
去检查一下
Get checked out.
我们待会再碰头
We'll regroup later.
你不知道拉响那个铃对我有多痛苦
You have no idea how much that killed me to ring that bell.
你的表现很好
You played your part well.
-现在呢  -现在开始才是真正的任务
- Now what? - Now, the real work begins.
欢迎加入"俄里翁"
Welcome to Orion.
我是谁  凯西
Who am I, Casey?
俄里翁
Orion.
这个项目叫"俄里翁"
Program's called Orion.
告诉我  什么是"俄里翁"
Tell me... what's Orion?
你说什么
What did you say?
你要见我
You wanted to see me?
医生说你没事了吗
The medics cleared you?
没事  只是有几处擦伤
Yeah, just a few bad bruises.
今天早些时候你是怎么回事
What happened earlier today,
当着陆军刑事调查人员的面顶撞我
you challenging me in front of Army CID,
这种行为是无法接受的
that was unacceptable.
抱歉  我不是...
I'm sorry, I-- I wasn't...
我不是想顶撞你
I wasn't trying to challenge you.
这种事情不要有第二次
Just don't let it happen again.
我不是想顶撞你
I wasn't trying to challenge you,
但你不应该让他们带走查理
but you shouldn't have let them take Charlie.
那件事我无权决定  你更是无权决定
That wasn't my call to make and it certainly wasn't yours.
他很害怕  很无助
He was scared, helpless.
你应该再努力争取一下  让他继续关在这里
You should've fought harder to keep him in custody.
陆军刑事调查局有审判权
Army CID had jurisdiction.
我也无能为力
It was out of my hands.
如果我们没放他走  他现在可能还活着
If we hadn't let him go, he might still be alive.
干我们这一行
In this job,
就必须要接受一些你无法认同的决定
we all have to accept decisions that we don't agree with.
这就叫做指挥机制
It's called chain of command.
女士  他们在楼上等你了
Ma'am, they're ready for you upstairs.
如果你还想继续在这个团队里待下去
And if you are gonna remain part of this team,
就必须学会跟着团队的步调行事
you're gonna have to learn to function as part of a unit.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
明白
Yeah.
你知道你并不是他们中的一员
You know that you're not one of them...
你只是这个庞大机构中的一颗螺丝钉
that you're just a cog in their machine.
看起来很美味
Looks delicious.
尝起来更棒
Tastes even better.
莎拉说喝这个东西
Sarah says it's supposed to be good
对我的血小板什么的有好处
for my platelets or something.
要我说  这就像用玩具枪跟坦克斗一样
You ask me, it's like trying to stop a tank with a BB gun, but...
不过你也了解你妹妹
you know your sister.
要我帮把手吗
Do you want a hand?
莎拉最近交往的那个人  你知道多少
Do you know anything about this guy Sarah's out with?
她不想告诉我那个人的名字
Just that she won't tell me his name.
那一定是来真的了
Must be serious.
抱歉
Sorry.
-你看起来美极了  -谢谢
- You look amazing. - Thank you.
服务员戴的耳环比我的车还贵
The waitress's earrings cost more than my car.
不用管她戴了什么耳环  我喜欢你的车
Never mind her earrings, I like your car.
那可是辆古董车
It's-- it's an antique.
我点了你爱喝的甜饮料
I got you your usual sugar drink.
谢谢
Thank you.
干杯
Cheers.
那我就直接说了
Okay, I'm just gonna come right out and say it.
我很想你
I missed you.
我们两天前才见过面
I saw you two days ago.
两天前见的我就不能想你吗
I can't miss you after two days?
当然可以了  我还挺招人惦记的
Well, you sure can, I am pretty "miss-able."
你的脸怎么了
Oh, no, what happened to your face?
看起来很糟  实际没那么严重
Oh, it probably looks worse than what it really is.
我没事
I'm-- I'm fine.
你告诉我哥哥的时候他打的  对不对
My brother hit you when you told him, didn't he?
确实是工作时候伤的  不过不是他打的
Well, it is from work, but, no, he didn't hit me.
我还没告诉他
I didn't tell him.
-你个胆小鬼  -我知道
- You wimp. - I know, I know.
我会跟你哥哥说的
I-I-I'll speak to your brother.
我只是  想等到他没那么大压力的时候说
I just... trying to wait until he's not so stressed.
-你知道  -那永远等不到了
- You know. - So never.
你想让我来说吗
Do you want me to do it?
不不不  那样...听着
No, no, no, that's... look...
一定要由我来说
it has to come from me.
我只想确保能把话说清楚
I just want to make sure I do it right, you know?
我们开了三天车
Well, three-- three days we drove.
买那些票花了我一大笔钱
I paid a fortune for those tickets.
你妹妹一看到那个打扮成
And the second your sister saw that guy
布鲁托[米老鼠的忠犬]的人就激动哭了
in the-- in the Pluto costume, she burst into tears!
钱没白花
Money well spent.
那天晚上究竟发生了什么
What really happened that night?
泰勒失踪那晚
The night that Taylor disappeared.
你去哪了
Where were you?
你三小时前就离开了晚宴
You left that dinner party for three hours.
我自告奋勇去买酒
I volunteered for a booze run.
可我忘了买酒的地方
I'd forgotten that the liquor stores--
大多在周日不开门
most of them weren't open on Sundays.
周日的确不开
Sundays, yeah, I know.
所以你不得不开车去俄亥俄
So you had to drive halfway to Ohio.
对  我...
Yeah, I--
我不想听你骗了大家25年的谎话  爸爸
I don't want the line that you fed everyone for 25 years, Dad.
这就是实情
That's the truth.
你的鞋上怎么都是泥
Why were your shoes muddy?
你以为我睡着了
You thought I was asleep.
可我没有
I wasn't.
我看见你到家后用水冲鞋
I saw you hosing off your shoes when you got home.
我没有...
I didn't...
她还活着  科特
She's alive, Kurt.
那你为什么要隐瞒你去了哪儿
Then why did you lie about where you were?
因为我当时想自杀
Because I was trying to kill myself!
什么
What?
当年我抑郁了很久
I was depressed for a long time.
我早就想过自杀  可我下不了决心
And I had thought about it before and I just couldn't.
那天我终于受够了
And finally, I'd just had enough,
我开车去了萨斯奎哈纳河
and I drove to the Susquehanna,
走进了河里
and I walked... I walked in.
可这个情景一直挥之不去
And then I just couldn't shake this image.
什么情景
What image?
你和莎拉在参加我的葬礼
You and Sarah... at my funeral.
你们会穿什么
What-- what you'd be wearing...
坐在哪儿
where you'd be sitting.
所以我回到了车上
So I just, uh... got back in the car
开回了家
and drove home.
所以鞋上全是泥
With muddy shoes.
没错
Yes.
这么多年了
After all these years...
你为什么不告诉别人
why didn't you tell anyone?
谁会相信我
Who was gonna believe me?
我  莎拉
Me! Sarah!
妈妈
Mom!
我感到羞耻
I was so ashamed.
我差点就...
I had almost...
而且
And...
你们和你们妈妈绝对理解不了
Your-- and your mother never would've understood me.
反正莎拉从没相信过流言
Sarah, she never believed what people said anyway.
但你  我希望你
But you, I wanted you--
我希望你能离我远远的
I wanted you as far away from me as I could get you.
为什么
Why?
我总是满腔怒火
I was so full of rage.
我总是满腔...
I was so full of...
我不希望你变得像我一样
And I didn't want you to turn out like me.
对不起  柯特
I'm so sorry, Kurt.
我...
I'm-- I'm-- you know--
我很抱歉  柯特
I'm so sorry, Kurt.
我真的...
I'm so...
干得漂亮
Good work.
你怎么知道这是她的笔
How do you know it's hers?
如果两支笔真的一模一样
If they were really the same--
我知道
I know.
而我知道了你为什么会给我这个任务
And I know why you gave me this mission.
是吗
You do?
你想测试我的忠诚度  我合格了
It was a test of my loyalty, and I passed.
我信守了诺言  现在你欠我一些答案
I held up my end, and now you owe me some answers.
那个胡子大汉
The bearded man...
你不能相信他们
You can't trust them.
他是我们的人
Yes, he was with us.
他让我别相信"他们"
He told me not to trust "Them."
他指的是谁
Who did he mean?
联调局的人
The FBI.
是谁开枪打死他的
Why would-- who shot him?
换个问题
Ask me another question.
这个我现在不能告诉你
I can't tell you that yet.
给士兵注射ZIP害死他们的人
What about the people who gave ZIP to those dead soldiers?
也是我们的人吗
Were they with us, too?
不是  我们发现了那项研究
No. We found out about the research
并且不赞成这种做法
and disapproved of it.
但我们发现了一个对我们有帮助的应用
But we saw an application that was useful to us.
俄里翁是什么
What is Orion?
你今晚已经得到够多答案了
You already got enough answers tonight.
不  这对我不是游戏
No... this isn't a game to me.
俄里翁是什么
What is Orion?
俄里翁
Orion...
是你死去的地方
is where you died.